Privacy Policy
==============

Date updated: January 11, 2022

At Paul Pierce Photography, we are dedicated to keeping your interactions with us and on our site between you and us in each instance that we can. With that said, there are some instances where we must share your information with third parties in order to do business with you.

By continuing to use this website or otherwise accepting our Terms of Service, you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service of this website, which is owned and operated by Paul Pierce Photography.

What do we collect?
-------------------

In the normal course of visiting this website, we use cookies to help navigate our pages and provide a more efficient user experience.

At this time, we do not currently track our users via any analytic tools.

We use Google's reCAPTCHA service to prevent spam emails on our service, but we only use it to the minimum requirements to send email. Google recommends that reCAPTCHA be tagged on all pages of a website to help better track users, but this is a position that we reject for your privacy. It may mean that you are required to verify that you are not a robot every time you send an email to us via our contact page, but we think your privacy is worth the small inconvenience.

Information that you may provide voluntarily.
---------------------------------------------

Personal Information: You may provide your name, address, email address, phone number and other information via our contact feature solely at your discretion and we will protect it as best we can protect unencrypted email. To ensure that you are not put at greater risk than you like, do not include any information such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, or any other personal information that may be used to steal your identity or harm you in any other way. If you provide any such information, we cannot guarantee its safety and will not be responsible if it is intercepted or stolen by third parties. If we notice that an email with such information has come into our servers, we will delete it, but do not guarantee that unless you contact us. It may still have some residual digital footprint as servers are constantly backed up by our service providers.

If you accidentally provide too much personal information and would like it removed from our servers to the extent possible, please contact us via our contact form or at paul@paulpiercephotography.com with the subject “REMOVE PII” and we will follow up to remove your information.

Payment Information: Our website does not currently accept payments of any kind so please do not include payment information in any form on our site.

How we use and share your information
-------------------------------------

Here are some of the ways we may use and share your information:

To respond to your email inquiries.

To keep you informed of our products and services that may be of interest to you, or to inform you of third party products or services that may be of interest to you. We will not share your information with such third parties without your consent first.

To request feedback through email surveys.

To fulfill our legal and/or contractual obligations to you.

To comply with all lawful, law enforcement activities.

Information that you share with us will only be shared with those that must know it, such as our email providers, payment processing providers, shipping companies, and other companies as required to provide our services to you, but only what is absolutely necessary to do business.

California Don Not Track Disclosures
------------------------------------

Pursuant to the California Online Privacy Protection Act, we DO NOT honor “do not track” signals issued by browsers or other sources.

We do not currently track your activity through any first-party tracking features or third party tracking features.

We do not collect any user online activities over time or across different websites for any purpose including advertising or targeted ad serving.

Protection of Minors
--------------------

Our website does not market or intend for services or products to be marketed or provided to any individuals under the age of 18 years and we will not knowingly collect any information on any individual under the age of 18 years. If you become aware the a minor has provided us with their personal information, please contact us via our contact page or at paul@paulpiercephotography.com with the subject “REMOVE PII” and we will take steps to remove all the information that we control. If we become aware of such information on our own, we will take every step to remove the information as well.

Server Locations
----------------

Our servers are located in the United States and the internet laws of the United States shall govern all issues related to this website and the data collection and protection practices that we follow. AS mentioned in other sections, if any member of a country outside the United States would like their information deleted from our servers, they must contact us via our contact page or at paul@paulpiercephotography.com with the subject “REMOVE PII” and we will delete them at our earliest convenience.

Our website, products, and services are directed towards citizens and residents or the United States, however all website visitors are afforded the rights and protections as outlines above.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

We will occasionally make changes to our privacy policy to reflect new services we provide or laws that we must abide by. It will remain our policy to collect as little information on our users as possible, to track our users activity only as absolutely necessary to provide our services, and to NEVER SELL your information to any third party.

You are deemed to have accepted this policy and any amendments when you continue to access this website or purchase or use any of our products or services online.

We will update the date of the policy any time we make changes.

© 2024 Paul Pierce Photography
